还看报纸呢
Reading the paper?
你会失去那些
You are gonna lose
互联网上专属青少年的
All of your wired- teen- hyper- texting-
的时髦小玩意儿
Nano- gizmo street cred.
-我是叛逆分子  因为我守旧  -这里面
- I'm a rebel. I kick it old-school. - Is this
-加了奶油和两块糖  -谢谢
- Cream, two sugars. - Thanks.
时尚版  有值得关注的吗
The style section. Anything I need to know?
70年代的风格又流行回来了
The '70s are back.
像时空英豪(不死武士的电影)  拥有不死之身
They're like The Highlander. They just won't die.
早上好  妈妈  你今天走得真早
Good morning, Mother. You're dressed early.
我早上有课
Oh, I have class.
我觉得这事儿值得讨论
I believe that's a matter of some debate.
在新学校  有趣的人
At the new school, funny man.
我不是
Look, it's- it's not
不感激你做的一切
That I don't appreciate everything you've done-
但是女生必须要自己独立
But a girl has to stand on her own two feet.
你教什么课
What's the class?
生命教练入门
Introduction to life coaching.
我一直渴望做些有意义的事
It's- it's always been my desire to make a difference,
不管是在台上还是台下
Whether onstage or off, and...
名片都做好了
I... Have had cards made.
那是我的  这上面说我也是你的客户
That's my- I'm- you - it says here I'm your client.
你当然是
Well, of course you are.
我不是一直都在指导你的人生吗
Haven't I been telling you what to do your whole life?
老爸  朱莉·施密特的爸爸又进戒毒所了
Oh, uh, dad, Julie Schmidt's father is back in rehab,
那你能在华盛顿之旅当护花使者了
So a spot opened up to chaperone the D.C. trip.
那个在哪儿  你怎么知道
Where is the- how did you know
朱莉的爸爸的事
Julie's dad was back in rehab?
因为有互联网上青少年的小玩意儿
Must be a wired-teen-hyper-nano thing.
你觉得怎么样
So what do you say?
对不起  孩子  但你不在家
Sorry, kiddo, but, uh, with you away,
我的保护欲只能留在家了  还记得
My chaperoning needs reside here, or are you forgetting
上次奶奶一个人在家发生了什么吗
What happened the last time we left her alone?
她也就开了个小聚会
So she... had a little party.
墙上到处都是石灰粉片
There were lime shards embedded in the walls.
那天是击溃法国纪念日
It was Cinco de Mayo.
没错
Exactly.
我听到死亡的声音了
I hear dead people.
谁被谋杀了  吓人吗
Who was murdered, and was it gruesome?
这名受害人
One victim-
唐纳德·肯德尔  18岁
Donald Kendall,18.
雷丁预科高中的一名高三学生
He was a senior at Redding Prep.
他要错过毕业舞会了
Someone's gonna miss prom night.
雷丁预科高中
Redding Prep?
派克大街(纽约市豪华大街)的一所私立学校
Private school on Park Avenue.
有钱人的孩子上的学校
No trust fund baby left behind.
-他怎么会在船里  -不清楚
- What's he doing in the boat? - No idea.
-帕里什法医  怎么样  -有点怯场
- Dr. Parish, how are you doing? - Feet are cold.
那有什么有用的信息吗
So what do you got for me?
胸部中了一枪   大口径手枪
Single G.S.W. to the chest, fairly large caliber.
船里血量很少
And from the lack of blood inside the boat,
所以他并不是在船上遇害
I'd say he wasn't killed at sea.
有人移动过他
Somebody moved him.
他的鞋子上都是土和草
He's got dirt and grass all on his Chucky t's.
并不像是亡灵之旅
Other than the postmortem voyage,
是被抛尸在这儿
Looks like a pop and drop.
死亡时间推算是昨天深夜
I'm guessing sometime late last night.
有人把他拖到这儿的
Well, somebody dragged him here.
死亡地点不可能太远
He couldn't have come from very far.
让同事们在周围搜查看看
Let's get uniforms down here to do a perimeter walk.
从船一直第五大道
Get 'em to go from the boats over there down to fifth.
告诉他们要找的是大滩血迹
And tell 'em they're looking for a blood pool
-可能还有子弹壳  -收到
- And possible shell casings.  - Roger that.
埃斯波西托  查过船库了没
Esposito, did you check the boathouse?
还没
Not yet.
为什么要葬在船里
So why the burial at sea?
维京人相信  如果你想
The Vikings believed that if you wanted
死后进入英灵殿  就需要一艘船
To reach Valhalla, you needed a vessel.
持枪的维京人  又是你的故事
Gun- toting Viking- that's your theory?
不  不是
No, no, no.
他们还会要一个女人
They also launched their dead with a sacrificial woman...
美酒和一匹好马作为祭品
And some booze and a good horse.
灵书妙探 第一季第三集
Castle S01E03
你知道他在这个公园做什么吗
Do you know what he would've been doing in the park?
不知道
No.
你上次见到你儿子是什么时候
When was the last time you saw your son alive?
昨天  他去上学的时候
Yesterday, uh, when he left for school.
你知道他放学后可能会去哪儿吗
Do you know maybe where he went after?
他通常和朋友们在一起
He was usually with his friends.
他不回家吃晚饭吗
He didn't come home for dinner?
大多数情况  唐尼在外面吃或在别人家吃
Most nights, Donny ate out or at someone else's place.
他和雷丁高中那群好朋友在一起
He hung out with a pretty tight crowd at Redding.
他们从初中时就一起玩了
They've all been together since grammar school.
唐尼原来也常带他们回家吃饭
Donny used to have them over all the time.
只是  你们最近搬家了
Only, you’ve moved recently.
-是的  几个月前  -我是雷曼公司的股东
- Yes, a few months ago. - I was a partner at Lehman.
雷曼破产  我们损失很大
When it went under, well, we- we took a big hit.
这对一个十几岁的孩子来说很难适应
That can be pretty tough on a teenager.
已经习惯了某种生活方式
You get used to a certain way of living,
但这不是任何人的错
But it was no one's fault.
你觉得唐尼有因此而消沉吗
Do you think Donny was depressed?
没有  唐尼很坚强
No, Donny was strong.
但失去你拥有的一切
But to lose everything you have...
我们只是还过得去而已
We were just getting by.
对于你们的情况  我很遗憾
I'm very sorry for your loss.
你怎么知道他们搬过家
How did you know they moved?
除非肯德尔夫妇是真的喜欢艺术
Either the Kendalls really like art
否则那个中国屏风
Or that Chinese screen was meant for
该摆在更大的公寓里
A much bigger apartment.
我在想  他们怎么付得起雷丁的学费
I wonder how they could still afford Redding.
-你知道那所学校  -纽约的
- You know the school?  - Oh, I've been kicked out
所有的优秀学校都开除过我
Of all of New York's finer educational institutions
至少一次
At least once.
讽刺的是  因为我现在有钱又有名
The irony is, now that I'm rich and famous,
他们都说我是校友  想让我捐钱
They all claim me as alum and want money.
-像你这真辛苦  -我该忍受的苦难
-It is just so rough being you. -My cross to bear.
当肯德尔夫妇说他们付不起学费时
When the Kendalls said they couldn't afford tuition,
我们给唐尼提供了奖学金
We put Donny on scholarship.
他们家曾经对学校非常慷慨
The family had been very generous in the past,
而且唐尼也是最棒的学生之一
And Donny was one of our brightest.
我们认为他会有很好的未来
We thought he'd do great things.
您知道他那么晚
Any idea what he would've been doing
在中央公园做什么吗
In Central Park at night?
好吧  事实上
Well, the truth is,
我们对这些孩子的了解  都只是冰山一角
All these kids are icebergs. We only see the tip.
如果你想知道其他信息
If you wanna know the rest,
你可能得和他的朋友们聊聊
You should probably talk to his friends-
阿曼达  罗米  布兰登  斯宾塞和麦克斯
Amanda, Romy, Brandon, Spencer and Max.
少了唐尼感觉很奇怪
It's strange seeing them without Donny.
谢谢
Thank you.
Thanks.
爆炸新闻  我爸妈去阿布扎比了
Breaking news- my parents are off to Abu Dhabi,
所以我家现在是自由区  晚上过来一起看
So I'm in a rents-free zone. Come over tonight for
与星共舞(真人秀节目)总决赛吧
The "Dancing with the Stars" results show.
七点半开始下注
Betting opens at 7:30.
然后开一桶我爸珍藏的16年份纯麦芽酒
My dad's cask- aged, 16- year- old single malt opens next.
那是在他家搬家和这事以前拍的
That was before they moved and everything.
你们中有谁昨晚和唐尼在一起吗
Were any of you with Donny last night?
我们放学的时候一起出去玩
We hung out after school,
但是五点左右就各回各家了
But we all headed home around 5:00.
你们知道他可能是为什么去公园吗
Do you know of any reason he'd be in the park?
孩子们  我上过约克预科
Look, you guys, I went to York.
我知道诚信制度  保护朋友
I know all about honor codes and protecting your friends.
你上过约克预科
You went to York prep?
那你怎么会当警察的
How does a Yorkie end up a cop?
天有不测风云  比如这样的事
Things happen. Things like this.
重点是  如果你们想要
Point is, is that if you're trying
保护你们朋友的隐私  我理解
To protect your friend's memory, I get it.
但总有一天会真相大白的
But eventually, the truth comes out.
但越快知道真相  我们就越容易
And the faster it does, the easier it'll be for us
找出凶手
To help find who did it.
他们家已经一无所有了
His family had lost everything.
虽然大家无所谓  但是我们要出去玩的
Not that we cared, but we go out, you know?
我们一直想帮他付  但他不愿意
We always offered to cover him, but he couldn't handle it.
-他有点儿崩溃了  -怎么个崩溃法
- Yeah, he just kinda fell apart. - Fell apart how?
各位  他不会再卷入任何麻烦了
Guys, he can't get in trouble.
他似乎染上毒瘾了
He kind of got into drugs.
如果他没钱了  怎么支持吸毒的开销
If he had money problems, how'd he support a drug habit?
他开始在公园做毒品交易
He started dealing... in the park.
经典悲剧
Classic tragedy.
显赫的家族衰落了
Prominent family falls into disrepute,
-第二代们开始堕落  -然后坏事就来了
- Scion spirals down... - And bad things happen.
坏事当然会来
Of course bad things happen.
否则就不叫悲剧了
Otherwise, it wouldn't be a tragedy.
知道吗  在希腊语里
Did you know, in the original Greek,
悲剧的字面意思  是指山羊之歌
"Tragedy" literally means "goat song"?
好吧  其实我也搞不懂
I know, it doesn't make any sense to me, either.
但不管开始的故事如何
But whatever that first story was,
我总是忍不住去想
I can't help but think
那只山羊肯定遭遇了非常悲惨的事情
Bad things must've happened to that goat.
是  好的
Yep. Okay.
当然  好的  我马上到
Of course. Sure, I’ll be right there.
下次用免提嘛
Next time, put it on speakerphone.
我会想看你
I'm gonna want to see the pictures of those
-穿格子裙和过膝袜的照片  -你说什么?
- Plaid skirts and knee socks. - Excuse me?
我看过约克预科的校服
I've seen those York school uniforms.
好吧  我想加入你的扑克游戏
Okay, I want in on your poker game.
我上的是公立学校
I went to public school.
我这么说是想让他们觉得亲切点
I just told them that to make them feel comfortable.
演得不错嘛  斯特里普女士(著名女演员)
Well played, Ms. Streep.
是像走出非洲里的她  还是妈妈咪呀里的
Which Meryl -"Out of Africa" or "Mamma Mia!"?
昨晚有人报警
So a 9-1-1 call comes in last night
大概是离这儿50米的地方
About 50 yards from here.
埃斯波西托正在追查  但我们发现这个
Esposito's following up, but we found this.
看着像泥巴  但其实是血迹
Looks like mud. It's actually blood.
表明他当时是坐在长凳上的
Figured he was sitting on top of the bench,
胸部中了一枪后
Takes one to the chest,
往后跌倒在这儿
Falls back over here...
然后被拖到了湖里
And then he's dragged to the lake.
晚上坐在公园的长凳上干嘛
So what's he doing sitting on a park bench at night?
我当缉毒警察时
During my Narc days,
这里是公开的交易场所
This area was pretty much an open bazaar,
-尤其是夜里  -交易失败
- Especially at night. - A drug deal gone bad.
接受过私立学校教育
Fancy private school education
也不代表就不蠢
Don't mean you aren't stupid.
当过缉毒警察也不怎么样
Neither does a career in narcotics.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
这是很大面积的一滩血
This is a very large pool of blood.
蕾妮说过  击中他的是大口径手枪
Lanie said he was shot with a large-caliber bullet.
如果这个孩子是刚被杀就被拖走
So if this kid is dragged when he's a fresh kill,
延着这条路上不是该有更多血迹吗
Wouldn't there be more of a blood trail?
也就是他在这儿躺了会儿
He was lying here for a while.
为什么会有人回来把他移走
Why would someone come back and move him?
如果凶手是毒贩子  那么他会意识到
If it was a drug dealer, then he's gonna realize
尸体放在这儿
The cops are gonna think drug dealer
警察会想到毒贩子
If they find a body here.
就增加了他被逮到的几率
Increasing his chances of getting caught.
所以他把尸体拖到了那边
So he drags the body over there
只是为了转移我们的注意力
Just to try to throw us off.
我不明白  卡塞尔
I don't know, Castle.
一个聪明的毒贩
A smart drug dealer?
一切都在进化  为什么罪犯不能
Ah, everything evolves. Why not criminals?
她报的警
9-1-1 caller?
是的  法尔西诺太太
Yeah, Mrs. Falcigno-
昨晚遛狗时听到枪声
Was walking her dog when she heard the shot last night.
她说几秒钟后
A few seconds later,
看见一个白人从她身边跑过
Said she saw a white dude run past her.
我让她看看嫌犯照片
I got her looking through mug books
都是在这一带抓到的毒贩
At dealers arrested in that area.
警官  快过来
Hey, detective, get over here!
看到你认识的了吗  法尔西诺太太
See someone you recognize, Mrs. Falcigno?
不  我想念你才情洋溢的人格魅力  当然
No, I miss your sparkling personality. Yeah!
-我当时看到的就是这家伙  -你确定
- That's the guy I saw right here. - You sure?
还要给我测谎吗  就是他
What, do you want to give me a lie detector? That's him!
知道你为什么在这儿吗
Do you know why you're here?
不知道
No idea.
逮捕你的警官说他曾看到你
The arresting officer said that he saw you
在公园进行毒品交易
In a hand-to-hand sale of narcotics in the park.
肯定是把我和别人弄混了
Must have me confused with somebody else.
是吗  你的意思是说
Really? Is that what you're giving me,
所有的毒贩子都长一个样
That all drug dealers look alike?
抓你可是人赃并获  斯科维尔先生
You were arrested with money and dope, Mr. Scoville.
而且事实上
Given the fact that
你可是早有两起重罪在身
You have two prior felony sales on your sheet,
你最好
You should probably
赶紧交代一切
Come up with something better pretty quick.
为什么你要这样跟我作对
Why you jammin' me up like this?
你昨天晚上在公园干什么
What were you doing in the park last night?
什么让你肯定我昨晚在公园
What makes you think I was even in the park?
一个非常可信的证人说她看见你
A very reliable witness said she saw you
半夜跑向72大街的方向
Runnin' toward 72nd street about midnight.
她不是该一针见血
Shouldn't she put him on his heels,
直接问枪杀案吗
Go straight for the shooting?
关键不在于这个
It's not about putting him on his heels.
主要是让公诉人立案
It's about building a case for the D.A.
那又怎么了  我在公园跑步  怎么样
So? I was running in the park. So what?
她已经让他承认曾在犯罪现场了
See? She just got him to put himself at the crime scene.
跑步不犯法  但是开枪杀人犯法
So running isn't illegal, but shootin' someone is.
开枪  杀人
Shootin' someone?
认识这个人吗  唐尼·肯德尔
Do you recognize his person- Donny Kendall?
从没见过
Never seen him before.
是吗  为什么我感觉
Really? How come I'm getting the feeling
你并没有完全跟我说实话呢
That you're not being completely truthful with me?
看她  看好了
Watch this. Watch her now.
我想要豁免权
I want immunity.
怎么获  因为你的腮腺炎
From what? The mumps?
你知道什么是第三次的失败者吗  斯科维尔
Do you know what a 3- time loser is, Scoville?
第三次被控重罪的人  要判无期徒刑
It's a person facing a third felony conviction,
事实上  我说的就是你
Someone just like you, in fact.
好吧  我看见过他
All right. I seen him.
-昨天晚上  -是的  昨晚
- Last night?  - Yeah, last night.
现在把他和受害人联系起来了
Just placed him with the victim.
你卖毒品给他了
You sell to him?
没有
No.
你是个毒贩  怎么认识他的
You're a drug dealer. How'd you know him?
通过你的牌友们
You poker buddies?
跟你交谈真愉快啊  斯科维尔先生
It was real nice chatting with you, Mr. Scoville.
也许25年后你能写信给我
Maybe you can drop me a line in about 25 years.
等等  我都说  我全都说
All right, all right, hold up. Hold up. All right!
我卖给他了
I sold to him.
什么时候
When?
昨晚
Last night.
有好几次  卖给他和他的小伙伴们
Bunch of other times, too, him and his little buddies.
小伙伴
What little buddies?
不知道  都是小孩子  大概是他的朋友
I don't know. Kids. Friends of his.
说清楚点
Describe 'em.
几个男的  几个女的  有一个是亚洲人
A couple of dudes, a couple of chicks. One was Asian.
身材还挺辣的
Kinda hot.
你是说  昨晚你看见他们全部
Okay, so you're telling me that you saw all of them
都在公园  对吗
In the park last night, right?
现在我们找到证人了
And now we got some witnesses.
说谎的证人
Witnesses who lied.
你们没跟我说实话
You guys lied to me.
唐尼中枪的时候你们都在  是不是
You were all with Donny when he got shot, weren't you?
知道什么叫妨碍司法公正吗
Anyone know what obstruction is?
如果你们在罪案调查中
I believe that's when you deliberately
蓄意提供虚假信息
Give false information in a criminal case.
是要坐牢的
You go to prison for it.
麦克斯
Max?
阿曼达
Amanda?
没错  我们在那儿
Yeah, we were there.
你们当时在公园
You were at the park?
唐尼已经失控了  我们只是想阻止他
Donny was out of control. We were just trying to stop him.
我怎么觉得你没说实话
Why don't I believe you?
伙计们  说出真相吧
Guys, just tell the truth.
有时候  我们也会去公园
Sometimes we'd go to the park, too.
然后跟父母说
We'd tell our parents
我们去其中一个人的家里玩
We're hanging out at one of our apartments,
但实际上我们去公园或者聚会
But we'd actually go to the park and party,
然后唐尼就会
And Donny would-
给你们任何想要的东西
Would get you whatever you wanted.
到底发生了什么
So what happened?
我们当时在一起  玩得很开心
We're all just hanging out, having a good time, partying.
然后那家伙走过来  搞砸了一切
And this guy came over, and he's a messed up,
他拿着把枪  而且他
And he's got this gun. And he- and he's-
他冲着唐尼喊
He's yelling at Donny
我的钱呢  我他妈要我的钱
"Where’s my money? I need my friggin' money!"
唐尼欠他两百块  但当时身上没钱
Donny owes him 200 bucks. Donny didn't have it.
那个人用枪指着他  然后听到砰的一声
Then the guy points the gun. And there's this loud pop,
唐尼就倒在地上了
And you just see Donny's body crumple.
那你们呢
What did you guys do?
我们跑了 我们吓跑了
We ran. We just ran.
你们没想到要报警吗
You didn't think to call the police?
他死了
He was dead.
我们知道他死了  如果报警了
I mean, we knew he was dead. Calling someone-
你们就会有麻烦了
Would have just gotten you into trouble?
你们看清楚了那个人的长相吗
Did you get a good look at this guy?
能指认他吗
Do you think you'd be able to identify him?
当时天很暗
It- it was dark.
唐尼坐在长椅的另一头
You know, Donny was at the end of the bench.
那谁离得最近
Who was the closest?
罗米  别紧张  这很简单
Okay, Romy, this will be easy.
百叶窗拉开
And when we raise the shades,
他们也看不见你的
they won't be able to see you.
真的吗
Are you sure?
我保证
I promise.
他们不会知道我们在这儿
They have no idea who's back here.
如果认出某个人  告诉我就好  行吗
You just let me know if you recognize anyone, okay?
请把百叶窗拉开
Raise the shades, please.
一号  向前走
Number 1, step forward.
后退  一号
Step back, number 1.
后退
Step back.
二号
Number 2.
二号  向前走
Number 2, step forward.
认出什么人了吗
Do you recognize anyone?
二号
Number 2.
你在哪儿见过他
Where do you recognize him from?
在公园里
The park.
是他杀了唐尼
He shot Donny.
又在想着
Are you trying to figure out
怎么在别人睡觉时谋害他吗
how to murder someone in their sleep again?
这次不是
Not this time.
知道吗  你小的时候
Do you know when you were little,
我每天都看着你睡着  才去睡
I used to watch you sleep every night before I went to bed,
就看几分钟
Just for a few minutes.
你那时候真是太可爱了
It was ridiculous how adorable you were.
谁会知道  这么多年过去了
Who'd have thought, all these years later,
你还是这么可爱呢
You're still adorable?
打呼噜和流口水有什么可爱的
What part of snoring and drooling is adorable?
每呼吸10到15次  你会发出点小噪音
Well, every 10 or 15 breaths, you make a little snort noise.
有时候甚至吹起泡泡
And then sometimes you'll even get a little spit bubble-
行啦  爸爸  到底什么事
Okay, dad. Seriously.
-你有没有碰毒品  -没有
- Do you do drugs? - No.
真的  其实你可以告诉我的
Are you sure? Cause you can tell me.
-爸爸  你觉得我嗜睡  异常暴躁吗  -没有
- Dad, am I lethargic and uncharacteristically irritable? - No.
我的眼睛无缘无故会充血吗
Are my eyes bloodshot for no apparent reason?
除非你病了
No, except when you're sick.
-这是有缘有故  -什么
- Well, that's an apparent reason. - What?
-我的成绩突然下滑了吗  -没有
- Are my grades plummeting? - No.
根据纽约市家长及教师准则
Then according to New York City's guidelines
可以肯定  我是没有吸毒的
For parents and teachers, it's a pretty safe bet I'm clean.
你分析得很棒
You make an excellent case.
其实毒品聚会是邀请家长的
Parents are invited to the drug assemblies.
你下次应该来看看
You should come next time.
毒品聚会
Drug assemblies?
现在的孩子都这么说吗
Is that what the kids are calling 'em nowadays?
还提供点心的
They serve cookies.
哪些朋友会
And which of your friends
会跟你去这个聚会
are going on this D.C. Jamboree with you?
泰勒  凯尔茜  还有佩奇
Taylor, Kelsey and Paige.
我怎么知道  他们是不会带毒品
Okay, how do I know they're not bringing the blow
在酒店开派对的人
And partying winehouse-style?
因为你很了解他们
Um, because you know them really well,
知道他们是好孩子
and they're good kids?
我的了解可能只是冰山一角
But maybe they're icebergs.
你说这些  是跟雷丁那个男生有关吗
Does this have something to do with that Redding kid?
爸爸  他大半夜待在中央公园
Dad, he was in Central Park really, really late at night.
我从来不会那样的
That's something I would never do.
其实如果你做过  可以告诉我
But if you did, you could tell me.
我不想让你  非得跟我说谎
I don't want you to feel you ever have to lie to me.
无论你和朋友们做过什么
Anything you and your friends have done,
相信我  我都干过更糟的
believe me, I've done worse.
我知道
I know.
不过好消息是  我不是你
But the good news is, I'm not you.
我是说  你不用担心
I just mean you don't have to worry.
而且  就算我有什么麻烦
Besides, if I ever got in any real trouble,
我的朋友们会帮我搞定
My friends would be there to bail me out.
对
Right.
朋友就是这样的
Because that's what friends do.
先生们  先生们
Gentlemen. Gentlemen.
不好意思  我要挂了
Excuse me, I gotta go. I gotta go.
为什么唐尼的朋友不给毒贩钱呢
Why didn't Donny's friends just give him the money?
在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
那些孩子身上总有现金
These kids always have cash.
你说说为什么这些朋友
You're gonna tell me
没有一个借他救命钱呢
one of them couldn't spring a few bucks to save his life?
卡塞尔  发疯的毒贩挥着把枪
Castle, some demented drug dealer's waving a gun.
他们大概吓傻了
Um, they probably froze up.
全部都是吗  他又不是在问高考题
But all of them? He wasn't asking S.A.T. questions.
他只是要钱
He was asking for money
这些孩子睡着了都会数钱
Something these kids probably count in their sleep.
这个斯科维尔是个坏家伙
Look, this Scoville is a bad dude,
而且证据确凿
And we got more than enough.
对  有那个女孩  我们赢定了
Yeah, with the girl, it's a slam dunk.
你们怎么找到那个女孩的
And who gave you the girl?
斯科维尔说的
Scoville.
所以这家伙并不聪明
So the guy's not a genius.
行行行  就算你是对的
Okay, okay. Say you're right.
这些孩子为什么咬定一个不相干的人谋杀
Why would these kids peg the wrong guy for a murder?
简单  他们中的一个是真凶
Simple- one of them did it.
你好  贝克特
Hey, Beckett.
扬克姆安
Yankman.
-这位朋友是谁啊  -他是
- Who's the sidekick?  - He's a...
-顾问  -顾问
- Consultant?  - Consultant.
那你是不是该在抓错人之前
Yeah? Well, uh, shouldn't you consult the consultant
咨询一下你的顾问呢
Before you arrest the wrong guy?
我还不确定是否抓错人  扬克姆安
I'm not sure I have the wrong guy yet, Yankman.
我的当事人不高兴了
Well, my client's not happy.
是他为你们提供的潜在证人
He gave you potential witnesses,
你们却用其中一个来对付他
And then you used one against him.
你的当事人并不乐意提供消息
Yeah, well, your client wasn't exactly forthcoming.
但是  如果他肯向我坦白一切
But I'm willing to reconsider
我会重新考虑的
If he tells me everything he knows.
别相信她
Don't trust her.
想想你是怎么被控谋杀的
Seeing as how you're facing a murder charge,
为什么不听大家的意见呢
Why don't you just go with the flow?
小顾问是对的  你是破罐子破摔了
Consultant boy is right. You got nothing to lose.
唐尼被杀那晚
The night that Donny was killed,
你卖毒品给他和他的朋友了  是吗
You sold to him and his friends, right?
-没有  -没有吗
- No.  - No?
你这样是不会让她重新考虑的
That's not how you really get her to reconsider.
我没有卖给他
I didn't sell to him!
他们为我工作
They were workin' for me.
为你工作
Workin' for you?
我给那个小混蛋供货
I supplied that punk.
他的朋友也是从我这儿买进
All right? His friends bought off me, too.
他们再倒卖
Then they'd go play dealer,
给绵羊草地(中央公园景观)的上流客户
selling to the upscales up in Sheeps Meadow.
等等  他们替你卖毒品
Wait a minute. They sold for you?
唐尼是的  其他人游手好闲
Donny, yeah. The others, it was just like a goof,
他们的生活很疯狂  就像真心话大冒险
Like walk on the Wild Side, like Truth or Dare.
那么唐尼被杀的时候你在哪儿
So where were you when Donny got shot?
我当时跟一帮朋友
I was hanging with my boys down by
在爱丽丝梦游仙境雕塑那儿
The "Alice in Wonderland" statue.
我们什么都没看见  听到那声枪响就跑了
We didn't see nothing. We heard the shot, took off.
-那枪呢  -我告诉你了  我没带枪
- What about the gun?  - I told you, I don't pack.
记录显示他从未因为枪支获罪
Criminal record with no firearms convictions
听上去是说实话了
Does sort of give it the ring of truth.
如果过去不过是序幕  重新审查该怎么做
If past is prologue, how we doing on reconsideration?
如果不想回答就算了
Don't have to answer if you don't want.
我知道答案  任何时候
I know the answer. Anytime.
任何时候  贝克特
Anytime, Beckett.
你们跟我开玩笑吧
You gotta be kidding me.
我已经告诉上头说抓到人了
I already told the brass that we got the guy.
我知道这比较尴尬
I can see how that'd be a little awkward.
市长都打电话来感谢我
The mayor even called to thank me.
-他会去看尼克斯队(NBA球队)的比赛  -很好
- He's in for the Knicks game, by the way.  - Sweet.
大家都希望这个残暴的毒贩是凶手
Look, I know everyone likes the violent drug dealer for this-
不  是非常非常希望
No, we love the violent drug dealer for this.
但残暴的毒贩的口供
Only the violent drug dealer's story
比证人的更可信
makes more sense than our witness'.
虽然我是新来的  但是
Plus- and I know I'm new here but-
你们应该抓住真凶是吗
Aren't you supposed to arrest the right guy?
好  再去跟那个女孩谈谈
Okay, go and talk to the girl again.
但是没有我的命令  毒贩谁都不能放
But my violent drug dealer stays where he is until I say so.
球赛见
I'll see you at the game.
收到
Got it.
你说过毒贩向唐尼索要
So this dealer asked Donny
欠他的几百块
for the couple hundred he owed him,
-对吗  -没错
- Right?  - Yeah.
但是唐尼说他没这么多钱
And Donny told him he didn't have it?
是的
Right.
你介意我看一看你的钱包吗
You mind if I take a look at your purse?
她的钱包  为什么
Her purse? What for?
如果有需要  我可以申请搜查令
I can get a warrant if you want.
古奇的包
Gucci.
我的包跟这个有什么关系
What does my bag have to do with anything?
如果唐尼真是你的好朋友
If Donny was such a good friend,
为什么眼睁睁看着他被杀
Why did you let him get shot?
眼睁睁看着
Let him?
你用足够的钱付给那个人
You had more than enough money to pay off the guy.
我相信你们都有足够的钱
I bet you all had more than enough.
但是唐尼还是死了
And yet Donny is dead.
为什么没有一个人帮他还钱
Why didn't any of you front him the money?
你在暗示什么
What are you implying?
她没有暗示
She isn't implying.
她是直说  关于当晚
She's saying your daughter is lying about
你的女儿在说谎
about what happened that night.
根本就没有那个人  对吗  罗米
There wasn't a guy, was there, Romy?
我什么也没做
I- I didn't do anything.
罗米
Romy.
那晚唐尼到底怎么了
What really happened to Donny that night?
是场意外
It was an accident.
当时我们在玩游戏
We were just playing a game.
游戏
A game?
-有点像俄式轮盘赌  -罗米  用枪吗
- Like Russian roulette. - Romy! With a gun?
只是好玩  我们玩了好多回了
It was just for fun. We- we did it all the time.
好玩
For fun?
-罗米你从哪儿来的枪  -斯宾塞的
- Where'd you get the gun, Romy? - Spencer had it.
我们没想到枪里有子弹
We never meant for there to be bullets.
我们只是用枪指着对方
We just pointed the gun at each other
扣动扳机  体验那一刻的感受
And pulled the trigger, just to see what it felt like.
-唐尼是怎么中枪的  -斯宾塞买的子弹
- Then how did Donny get shot? - Spencer bought bullets.
我们去他家在蒙托克(度假胜地)的避暑别墅
We went up to his summer house in Montauk
只是射击罐子和别的东西
Just to shoot around at cans and stuff.
一颗子弹无意中留在了枪里
One must have got left in by accident.
是谁  开枪打死了他
Who? Who shot him?
罗米  看着我
Romy, look at me.
是谁打死了唐尼
Who shot Donny?
麦克斯
Max.
是麦克斯
It was Max.
纽约市警察局  凯特·贝克特探长
Detective Kate Beckett, NYPD.
我要找麦克斯·海勒  他在这吗
I'm looking for Max Heller. Is he here?
不在  我是她妈妈  怎么了
No. I'm his mother. What's going on?
海勒太太  我现在要见他
I need to see him right now, Mrs. Heller.
-你知道他在哪儿吗  -不知道  怎么了
- Do you know where he is? - No, I don't. What is it?
这是他的逮捕令
I have a warrant for his arrest.
逮捕令  天哪  为什么
A warrant? Oh, my god. For what?
因为他犯了谋杀罪  海勒太太  你明白吗
He's wanted for murder, Mrs. Heller. Do you understand?
请你往他的手机打个电话
I need you to go and call him on his cell phone,
问他在哪儿  告诉他别动
Find out where he is, tell him not to move.
一切都会没问题的
Everything is gonna be all right,
但请你现在就去打电话
But I need you to do it now.
埃斯波西托警官会和你一起
Detective Esposito will go with you.
-拿张他的照片放进详细情报  -好的
- Get a photograph of him for the A.P.B., please. - Right.
探长
Detective.
什么  在哪儿
What? Where?
这孩子不接电话
The kid's not answering his cell phone.
他妈妈猜他可能去了公园
Mom thinks maybe he went to the park.
他去了公园  自杀了
Yeah, he went to the park... And killed himself.
那现在呢  我该做点什么
So what now? What should I do?
怎么了
What?
爸爸  我说谎了
I lied to you, dad.
-等等好吗  -不  我要告诉你
- Oh. Can this wait? - No. You need to know.
那好吧
Oh. Yeah.
好  当然
Yeah, o- okay.
记得那个假日聚会吗
Remember the holiday formal,
之后我和凯尔茜是怎么离开泰勒家的
How Kelsey and I went to Taylor's house after?
我们离开的时候  天开始下雨
Well, when we left, it was already raining,
我们花了半小时打出租车
And we tried for, like, half an hour to get a taxi,
还是没打到车
But we couldn't,
我们都湿透了很冷
and we were already so soaking wet and cold
于是最后决定去坐地铁
That we finally decided to take the subway,
尽管已经十点多了
Even though it was way after 10:00.
但考虑到  在雨中打到车的可能性
Well, considering that getting a cab in the rain
就像强力球(美国全国性彩票)中头奖
Is kind of like winning the Powerball jackpot,
我原谅你了
I forgive you.
不是  听着  2号线有车来了
No, listen. The 2 was coming,
凯尔茜跑过大门
And Kelsey ran through the door
下楼去帮我开着门
And was going down the stairs to hold the door for me,
但我刷卡的时候  已经没钱了
But when I swiped my card, it was empty,
我没时间去充钱
And I didn't have any time to add any more money to it,
凯尔茜叫我快点过去  所以我
And Kelsey was screaming for me to come, and I was-
我很累  急着回家
I was just so tired, and I was just anxious to get home,
-爸爸  我都不想说了  -怎么了
- That, dad... I don't even want to say it. - What?
我跳过栅门  逃票了
I jumped the turnstile.
那你坐上地铁了吗
Did you make the train?
坐上了  关键是我没告诉你
Y- yeah, but- but the point is, I didn't tell you,
尽管昨天你那么好  那么担心我
Even after you were so sweet and concerned yesterday.
-对不起  -你真的跳过栅门了
- I'm sorry. - Oh, you actually jumped the turnstile?
第二天我刷了两次卡
But I swiped my card twice the next day
但是我都没坐
And didn't even ride.
好吧  宝贝  如果
Okay. Oh, sweetie. If that-
如果这是你做过的最差劲的事
If that's the worst thing you've done,
那我真是个幸福的父亲
I'm a happy, happy man.
但是我说谎了  难道你不惩罚我吗
But I lied to you. Shouldn't you punish me?
当然了
Yes. No, you're right.
冰激凌做为早餐  无条件执行
Um... Mandatory ice cream for breakfast. No excuses.
我是认真的  我会自己惩罚自己
I'm serious. If you won't, I will.
冰激凌的惩罚  我也是认真的
I'm serious about the ice cream.
好吧  这个礼拜我禁足
Fine. I'm grounded for a week.
-虽然苛刻但也合理  -在华盛顿之行后吧
- All right. You're tough but fair. - After the D.C. Trip.
真是我的好女儿
That's my girl.
谢谢你  爸爸
Thanks, dad.
-在干吗呢  -一些文件
- What you doing? - Paperwork to dismiss
要撤销对斯科维尔的指控
The homicide charges against Scoville.
弹道学证实  麦克斯自杀的这把枪
Ballistics confirms that the gun used on Donny
就是当晚在公园里
In the park that night was the same one
杀害唐尼的那把
Max used on himself.
我擅长揣摩人的心思
I'm usually better at reading people.
你和麦克斯呆了半小时
You spent half an hour with Max.
你不可能看清楚整件事
There's no way you could have seen that coming.
可怜的孩子  肯定很痛苦
Poor kid must have been a mess.
想象枪杀你最好的朋友
Imagine shooting your best friend
但你不得不一直隐瞒此事
And then having to lie about it.
他可不只是隐瞒此事
Well, he did more than just lie about it.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
他回到案发地点  搬走了他朋友的尸体
He went back and moved his friend's body.
镇定自若地移尸
Having the presence of mind to move the body
这跟他的内疚情绪是否自相矛盾
Isn't exactly consistent with a guilty conscience, is it?
我想说  这超过了冷血杀手之所为
I'd say that's more an act of a cold-blooded killer.
冷血杀手不会突然有内疚感
And a cold-blooded killer doesn't suddenly feel guilty
而去自杀  对不对
Enough to commit suicide, does he?
我的小说里没写过
Not in any story I'd write.
如果我们没错  不是麦克斯移尸
So if we're right and Max didn't move Donny's body,
那会是谁呢
Then who did?
看起来像是普通的自杀案
Looks like your basic, garden- variety suicide.
但是你在电话里说有些疑点
But you said on the phone that there was something
是与自杀有矛盾的
That wasn't consistent with a suicide.
看起来像是自杀
Looks like suicide.
但仔细研究他开枪的手
But his shooting hand- more specifically,
右手食指有细微的擦伤
His right index finger- has a slight abrasion
在显微镜下才能看到  在验尸报告里
Visible only under the scope. Department autopsy protocol
可是一点儿都没提
Doesn't even call to look for that kind of thing.
你怎么看这处擦伤
And the abrasion means what to you?
另有其人帮他扣动了扳机
That someone may have helped him pull the trigger.
毒理分析显示他的血液酒精含量为0.28
Plus toxicology has his blood alcohol content at.28.
-0.28  -所以他喝醉了
- .28! - So he was drunk
酩酊大醉
Way drunk.
酒精含量0.28  他可能毫无知觉
At.28, he may not have even been conscious.
所以麦克斯是被谋杀的
So Max was murdered.
导演麦克斯自杀的人  想让我们相信
Whoever staged Max's suicide wanted us to believe that
他的自杀是由于杀死唐尼的负罪感
He killed himself out of guilt over shooting Donny,
这让我相信不是麦克斯杀死唐尼
Which makes me think Max didn't kill Donny after all.
但其他孩子证实了罗米的描述
The other kids corroborated Romy's story
是麦克斯扣动了扳机
That Max pulled the trigger.
我并非说不是他开的枪
I didn't say he didn't shoot him.
我说的是  不是他要杀唐尼
I said he didn't kill him.
是禅宗公案说的孤掌难鸣吗
Is that a zen koan "one hand clapping" thing? I...
这群孩子玩游戏
These kids played a game of pretending
假装朝对方开枪
To shoot at each other.
要是某人真的想让唐尼死呢
What if one of them wanted Donny dead for real?
还有什么能比
What better way than to
让别人替他扣动扳机更好呢
Get someone else to pull the trigger?
你认为在枪里放子弹的另有其人
You think one of the other kids put a bullet in the gun
-而麦克斯却不知道  -这个人就是凶手
- Without Max knowing? - That's our killer.
确实如此
Oh, I like that.
斯宾塞  子弹是你买的
You bought the bullets, Spencer.
我只是闹着玩而已
It was just to screw around.
你说的闹着玩  就是明明知道
If by "screwing around" you mean intentionally putting
麦克斯会向唐尼开枪
A bullet in a chamber knowing that
还把子弹放进枪膛
Max was gonna shoot Donny,
那就对了  我们意见一致
Then yes! You and I are in totally agreement!
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett
如果这个游戏的规则是  不用子弹开枪
If the point of the game was to shoot without bullets,
那你怎么会有子弹
Then why would you have bullets
除非你是故意的
Unless you intended to use'em?
我过告诉你
I told you, I didn't know
我不知道枪里有子弹
There were any bullets in the gun.
有人知道  而他就是杀麦克斯的凶手
Well, somebody did, and I think whoever it is killed Max.
你的枪  你的子弹
Your gun, your bullets-
从我的立场看  斯宾塞  你就是凶手
From where I'm standing, Spencer, you did it.
昨晚6点30分到9点之间你在哪儿
So where were you between 6:30 and 9:00 last night?
在我父亲的俱乐部
Uh... At- at my dad's club.
世纪俱乐部  和布兰登在一起
The Century. With Brandon.
你最好希望布兰登  能给你作证
You better hope that Brandon corroborates that.
我知道罗米和斯宾塞全都告诉你们了
Look, I know Romy and Spencer told you guys everything,
我们都有了麻烦
And that we're all in big trouble...
但是我很高兴
But I'm glad.
你很高兴
You're glad?
在意外发生之后
We should have just come clean with you guys
-我们就应该跟你们说清楚  -确实如此
- After the accident. - You're damn right you should've.
我知道  但我们不想给麦克斯带来麻烦
I know. But we didn't want to screw Max over.
这就是你们诬陷毒贩的原因  对吗
That's why you fingered the drug dealer, right?
他是可以牺牲的
'Cause he's expendable.
我告诉罗米这样不对  但她想保护麦克斯
I told Romy that was wrong, but she wanted to protect Max.
那个毒贩就是
And that junkie's the one
把唐尼拉进毒品交易的人
Who got Donny into dealing in the first place.
麦克斯被害的时候你在哪儿
So where were you when Max was killed?
和斯宾塞在他父亲的俱乐部
With Spencer at his dad's club.
问他  他能证明
Ask him, he’ll confirm it.
你们总是很坦白  是吗
You guys always have your stories straight, don’t you?
我们不在公园  那个毒贩是凶手
"We weren't at the park. It was the drug dealer.
是麦克斯  你们总是异口同声
It was Max. " You guys are always in sync.
所以  我不相信你们
Maybe that's why I don't believe you.
你可以不相信我
You don't have to believe me.
可是我有证据
I have proof.
知道吗  我们有视频
We'd take these videos, you know,
只是因为好玩  做疯狂的事情
I mean, just for laughs, doing crazy stuff.
罗米的父亲李先生是个电脑高手
Romy's dad Mr. Lee is like this big I.T. Guy,
他用蓝牙让我们的文件共享
And he hooked us up with a file share over bluetooth.
这样大家都有这些文件了
That way we'd all get the files.
阿曼达那晚拍的
Amanda shot this that night.
什么内容
What is it?
这个视频
A video...
是唐尼遭枪击的情况
Of Donny getting shot.
我们本应该删除的
We were all supposed to erase it.
但我知道如果真相大白
But I knew that if the truth came out,
我们就都有麻烦了
We'd all be screwed.
在杜克大学的强奸案里就是这样
And after what happened to those kids in that Duke case,
我只是
I just...
不想有那样一个结局
I didn't want to end up like that.
给你
Here.
喝光它  布兰
Oh, yeah, suck it down, Bran.
喝光  喝光  你真差劲
Suck it! Suck it! You suck.
小布兰登尿裤子了
Little Brandon wet himself!
太棒了  又被耍了  妈妈
Oh, great. "Punk'd" is back. Hi, mom!
好吧  我们开始吧  宝贝
All right, let's do this, baby!
你拉着我妈的海瑞·温斯顿(珠宝品牌)手镯
Hey, you pulled my mom's Harry Winston tennis bracelet.
-你偷的吧  -借的
- That you stole. - Borrowed.
这手镯顶我们全家的家当了
That's worth my entire family.
快来  伙计们  我的胳膊好累
Come on, guys. My arm's getting tired.
-我们开始吧  -开始喽
- Let's do this! - Okay, here we go.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
再见  安德森先生
Goodbye, Mr. Anderson.
天哪
Oh, my god!
你没事吧
You okay?
我在想唐尼的父母
I was just thinking about Donny's parents,
看到这个视频怎么受得了
What they'll go through when they watch that video.
我猜这种情况不多
Guess it's not too often
从录像带里抓住凶手
You get a murder caught on tape, huh?
他很聪明没删掉
Yeah, well, he was smart to keep it.
否则  他们都将面临谋杀的指控
Otherwise they'd all be facing a manslaughter charge.
是啊  很聪明
Yeah... That was pretty smart
当你想到这点的时候  对不对
When you think about it, wasn't it?
-我明白你的意思  卡塞尔  -我只是说
- I know that tone, Castle. - I'm just saying,
他们很幸运
It's pretty lucky
拍下了那晚的聚会
They filmed their little game that night.
人们在视频网站发布疯狂的事情
Yeah. Well, people post crazy stuff on You Tube.
刚开始拍的几次  很激动
I get filming it the first few times. It's exciting.
但是第10次  第15次呢
But the 10th? The 15th?
那个晚上有什么特别的呢
What was so special about that night?
唐尼中枪了
Donny got shot.
所以录像的唯一理由就是
So the only reason to film it is...
你知道要发生什么事
You knew something was gonna happen.
什么时候  谢谢你  肯德尔先生
And that was when? Okay, thank you, Mrs. Kendall.
得到消息
Get this
直到上个月唐尼和阿曼达一直谈恋爱
Donny and were dating until about a month ago.
唐尼和她分手了
When Donny broke it off?
今天没上学  阿曼达
You weren't in school today, Amanda.
怎么了  我对上学没兴趣
So? I wasn't up for it.
说谎会令人精疲力尽的
Yes. Lying can be so exhausting.
-又不是你们失去了朋友  -我们看到视频了
- So can losing two of your friends. - We saw the video.
布兰登告诉我了  你们都知道了
Brandon told me. So now you know everything.
那天晚上你们为什么录像
Why did you shoot the video that night?
我不知道  我们经常这样做
I don't know. We did lots of times.
那晚的上一次是什么时候
When was the last time before that night?
我不记得了
I don't remember.
你们不是说  你们什么都看见了吗
Look, I thought you said you saw what happened.
不错  可是为什么我们能看到
We did. We're just not sure why we saw what happened.
你们决定当晚录像
Your decision to make a video that night
这事解释不通
doesn't make any sense
除非你知道将要发生什么
Unless you knew something was gonna happen.
你说我知道吗  那完全是个意外
You think I knew? It was totally an accident!
我根本不可能会知道
There's no way I could have known
唐尼会中枪
Donny was gonna get shot.
当然可能
Sure there is,
如果是你在枪里放了子弹
If you're the one who put a bullet in the gun.
-什么  -我们和唐尼的父母谈过了
- What? - We spoke to Donny's parents.
你们曾经恋爱
We know you two were dating.
而且在一个月之前唐尼和你分手了
We also know Donny broke up with you about a month ago.
-天啊  -这就是你的动机  阿曼达
- Oh, my god. - It gives you motive, Amanda.
事情不是这样的
It's not what happened!
对  唐尼和我分手了
Yes, Donny broke up with me,
那只是因为他发现我和布兰登在一起
But only because he found out I hooked up with Brandon.
布兰登
Brandon?
都是因为他的家里
Everything with his family...
唐尼退出了
Donny checked out.
唐尼不在身边了  但是布兰登在
He wasn't there for me, and Brandon was.
我相信
I bet he was.
不是那样的  布兰登真是个好人
It's not like that. Brandon's a really good guy.
他是好人  还会留着那仅有的视频
A good guy who kept the only copy of a video
而且他说是你录的
He told us you shot.
如果他留着视频  自然有原因
If Brandon kept the video, he had his reasons.
当晚是布兰登让你录像的  对吗
Brandon told you to shoot the video that night, didn't he?
对
Yeah.
知道谁改口供了吗
Guess who just changed his story?
你哥们儿  斯宾塞
Your buddy Spencer.
他不能提供麦克斯死亡时  你的不在场证明
Your comrade just gave up your alibi for Max's murder.
你说麦克斯是自杀的  对吗
You mean Max's suicide, don't you?
而且我认为
And last I checked,
我不需要不在场证明  不是吗
I wouldn't need an alibi for that, would I?
法医鉴定
The medical examiner concluded
麦克斯是被谋杀的
That Max's death was a homicide.
我相信我们能雇到很多的专家
Oh. Well, I'm sure there are any number of experts
为我辩护
We can hire who will disagree with a city employee.
专家为你辩护  不在作案现场
Expert witnesses? Scrambling for alibis?
你好像已经准备好辩护了
Sounds like you're already building a defense.
你们不是一直
You guys have been running around
在我们中找谋杀凶手吗
Accusing everyone of murder.
我想该轮到我了  所以我最好有所准备
I figured my turn was coming, and I'd better be ready.
只是现在  我们知道你是凶手
Only now we know it was you.
麦克斯遇害那晚
All three of your friends have solid alibis
你的那三个朋友都有不在场证明
For the night Max was killed.
你说他是被杀  我说他是自杀
You say killed, I say suicide.
-那晚你在哪儿  -我去散步了
- Where were you that night? - I took a walk.
我知道你们不会相信
I knew you guys wouldn't believe me,
所以找斯宾塞打掩护
So I asked Spencer to cover for me.
你们总是互相打掩护  是吗
That's what you guys do, right, cover for each other?
没错  探长
Exactly. Look, detective,
你对每件事都感兴趣
You're hot in everything,
但如果你们有了确切的证据
But if you had any actual evidence,
早已经把我抓了
You'd have already arrested me.
我有视频能够证明麦克斯杀了唐尼
Me? I have a video that proves Max killed Donny.
你们真的认为陪审团会相信
Do you really think a jury's gonna believe
他没有喝醉  然后自杀吗
He didn't get drunk and off himself?
对你这只不过是个游戏  不是吗
This is just a game for you, isn’t it?
就像在公园里卖毒品
Like selling drugs in the park.
好吧  如果是  那我就赢了
Well, if it was, looks like I'd be winning.
不过  如果你认为我是凶手
But hey, if you think I did it...
就拿出证据来
Let's see you prove it.
我讨厌这孩子
I hate that kid.
你知道的  寻找证据真的很枯燥
You know, actually having to prove things is really tedious.
-欢迎加入我的世界  -布兰登策划了一切
- Welcome to my world. - Brandon had this all planned.
他借麦克斯之手杀死唐尼
He gets Max to shoot Donny
然后将麦克斯灌醉  杀了他
Then gets Max drunk and kills him.
世上没有完美的罪案  卡塞尔
There's no such thing as a perfect crime, Castle.
暂时没有  有一天我会写出完美的罪案
Not yet. But one day I'm gonna write it.
从72街公园入口到案发现场的
Okay, we canvassed every store, stand and homeless guy
商店摊位和流浪汉  我们全问过了
From the park's entrance at 72nd to the scene.
那晚没人见过麦克斯或布兰登
And no one remembers seeing Max or Brandon last night.
如果不能证明布兰登在作案现场
If we can't put Brandon at Max's murder scene,
那么检察官无法进一步行动
Then the D.A. Will never move.
那些孩子们互相传阅视频
These kids were hooked on video sharing.
一定有问题
There has to be something.
我已经查过所有有关的视频  音频
Eh, I already scrolled through every video, audio,
照片和短信
Photo and text file in that thing.
还是不够走运
Guess we weren't lucky enough
麦克斯没录下自己被布兰登谋害
To have Max take video of Brandon killing him.
有趣的是  如果他录了  布兰登会知道
Funny thing is, if he did, Brandon would have known.
那个文件会出现
It would have popped up
在他手机的共享文件中  只要他们的手机
In his shared folder as soon as their phones...
同步
Synced.
谢谢
Thank you.
同步
Synced.
麦克斯被杀时如果他们在一起
If they were together when Max was murdered,
那么他们的手机会自动同步
Then their phones would have automatically synced.
应该会有记录
There'd be a record.
你现在有权找位律师  布兰登
You have the right to have a lawyer present, Brandon.
如果你请不起  我们可以帮你安排
If you cannot afford one, one will be appointed to you.
他请得起身价百万的律师
Oh, he could afford a million lawyers.
-但她还是得告知我的权利  对吗  -对
- But she still has to advise me of my rights, right? - Right.
算了吧  我不需要律师
Anyway, that's cool. I don't want a lawyer.
这样会更有趣儿
This is way more fun.
那你就直接在这儿签字吧
Maybe you'd like to just sign a confession, then?
可以
Sure.
我承认
I confess...
对你上衣的里面很感兴趣
That I'm dying to cop a feel under your cop blouse.
就这样
There.
现在我感觉超好
Now I feel so much better.
你不想打电话吗
You sure you don't want to call somebody-
给你的父母
Your parents maybe?
我为什么要让他们担心
Why would I worry them?
刚才给我的赌注经纪打了个电话
You know, I made a call just a little while ago to my bookie.
好啊
Sweet.
我站在诺布(著名日式餐厅)外的大街上
I was standing in the street outside Nobu
等我的车
Waiting for my car.
我很喜欢那里
Oh, yeah? I love that place.
那里的鱿鱼意粉非常好
The black squid pasta is amazing.
服务生停车的时候
Anyway, I was talking on the phone
我一直在打电话
When the valet pulled up with my car.
突然  我的电话断了
And all of a sudden, my call got cut off.
这才想起  车里的蓝牙耳机
And I realized- oh, the bluetooth in my car
自动转接了电话  因为它们是连着的
Picked up the call automatically because they were linked.
你曾说过  你们的手机自动共享媒体文件
You told us that all your phones autoshare media files
-通过蓝牙连接  对吗  -怎么了
- Via a bluetooth link, right? - So?
所以在麦克斯被杀那晚
So your phone linked with Max's phone
你们俩的手机是连着的
The night he was killed.
这个数字指纹指出
It's a digital fingerprint that places you
麦克斯被杀时  你在离他6米的范围内
Within 20 feet of Max at the time of his murder.
你说过  如果她找到确实的证据
You did say if she got some actual evidence,
她应该逮捕你
She should arrest you.
你利用了麦克斯杀死唐尼的内疚感
You took advantage of Max's guilt over Donny's death,
然后灌醉了他
And you got him blackout drunk,
把枪放在他手里
And then you put a gun in his hand,
对准他的太阳穴
Pressed it against his temple,
扣动扳机
And then you pulled the trigger.
我为什么要这样做
Why would I do that?
用来掩饰唐尼是你杀的
To cover your tracks over killing Donny.
我为什么要杀唐尼
Why would I kill Donny?
阿曼达
Amanda.
阿曼达是我的  不是唐尼的
Amanda is with me, not Donny.
对  在唐尼家破产之后
Yeah, only after Donny lost all his money.
这让你感到有点失落吧
Which makes you sloppy seconds.
尤其是他得到的
Especially 'cause he got way more
不仅是上衣里面的
Than just under her blouse, right?
我有视频证明唐尼是麦克斯杀的
I have that video that shows that Max killed Donny,
我不是凶手
Not me.
你的安排  非常令人佩服
And arranging that was very impressive.
骗骗斯宾塞  罗米和阿曼达不是困难
Fooling Spencer, Romy and Amanda wasn't that hard.
因为他们不拿枪  不过麦克斯就不一样了
They didn't handle the gun. But Max was another story.
他的确扣动了扳机
He actually pulled the trigger,
他就是放不下  是不是
And he just couldn't let it go, could he?
后来他记起  是你给他的枪
And then he remembered, you gave him the gun.
所以他打电话给你  约你见面
So he called you and asked to meet you.
我们有通话记录
We have a record of the call.
你知道接下来会发生什么
You knew something was up,
所以你带着枪和什么呢  伏特加酒
So you brought the gun and, what, vodka?
或者麦克斯喜欢威士忌
Or was Max a scotch guy?
他知道你  阿曼达  和唐尼的事情
He knew all about you, Donny and Amanda.
他想到  是不是你设计圈套
He had to wonder," did you set me up
害我杀死了我最好的朋友
To kill my best friend?"
当他意识到是你
And when he realized you had,
他将不会保持沉默  是不是
He wasn't gonna keep it quiet, was he?
即使你告诉他  你们都将进监狱
Even with you telling him, " you'd all go to jail."
如果麦克斯足够强硬
If only Max had been strong enough just to man up...
如果唐尼能意识到
If only Donny realized
他和你们再没什么关系了
He didn't belong with you guys anymore,
他和阿曼达已经分手了  那么这一切
He and Amanda were through, well, then none of this
都没必要发生了
Would have been necessary.
弱者往往想不到的
Weak people just don't get it,
不是吗  布兰登
Do they, Brandon?
有时他们不得不被人领着  认识真相
Sometimes they just have to be led to the truth.
没错
Exactly.
他说的是  没错
Did he just say "exactly"?
-我听到他说  没错  -对  我也听见了
- Cause I heard him say "exactly". - Yeah, I heard it, too.
他设计我
He tricked me.
你们设计我
You tricked me.
这个叫做  不利于己的供认
It's called "admission against interest."
这个术语用在招供里真棒
It's just a fancy term for a confession.
很管用啊
Pretty sweet, huh?
有趣的是
Oh, and the funny thing is,
你肯定认为  回去搬走唐尼的尸体
I bet you thought you were pretty clever to go back
是神来之笔  是不是
And move Donny's body, right?
事实上
But the thing is,
如果你没这么做  我们就错过真相了
Is we would have never figured it out if you hadn't.
是的  她就错过真相了
Well, she would have never figured it out.
好像你能查出真相似的
Oh, like you would have figured it out.
我肯定可以的
I definitely would have figured it out.
你开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me right now?
诚实的  正经的  内心的想法
Honest truth, straight face, from my heart.
我们走  快  我不想迟到
Let's go. Power up. I don't want to be late.
你要去吗
You're coming?
我就是官方替补护花使者
You're looking at the official replacement chaperone.
我刚想起来
I just realized
有事要在华盛顿处理
I have some business to take care of in D.C. anyway.
是吗
Really?
以防万一  得为我的纪念馆选址
Yeah, I gotta pick out a spot for my monument just in case.
我觉得华盛顿和林肯
I think Washington and Lincoln
已经占了好地方
already have the good ones.
也许能把杰斐逊纪念馆挪挪
Maybe they can move Jefferson.
是的  肯定行
Oh, yeah, I'm sure.
你们俩要走了
All right, you two kids, hurry off now.
玩得开心些
You don't want to miss any of the fun.
-你是说你自己吧  -不是你想的那样
- Any of your fun, you mean? - It's not what you think.
不  和我想的一模一样
No, it's exactly what I thought.
这群人看起来很疯狂吗
Now does this look like a wild group?
告诉你  我举办的研讨会
For your information, I am hosting a seminar
是为了我的生命教练课程
For my life coaching class-
主题  为希望而改变
"Be the change you want to see."
-真有禅的意味  -老爸  支持点啦
- How very zen of you. - Dad, come on, be supportive.
-她也是想帮别人  -帮着喝光我的酒
- She's trying to help... People. - Yeah, to my liquor cabinet.
不  这会是一次非常文明的活动
No. This is going to be a very civilized affair.
走吧  走吧  玩得开心些
Now off, off, off, off. Have fun!